{"data":[{"question":"I saw Mrs Jones waiting_____ the bus stop.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"2"},{"question":"Susanne is ____ a meeting.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"2"},{"question":"George has his Spanish class _____ the morning.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"2"},{"question":"Write your name _____ the top of the page.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"2"},{"question":"I went to a nice restaurant _____ my birthday.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"2"},{"question":"My birthday is _____ March.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"2"},{"question":"Where do you eat when you're _____ the road?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"2"},{"question":"Do you work _____ Saturdays.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"2"},{"question":"I'm going on holiday ______ August.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"2"},{"question":"Professor Andrews only became famous _____ his old age.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"2"}]}